OK so now we'll look at what's called the past progressive or the past continuous.
好的，现在我们来看看所谓的过去进行或过去连续。
And again don't worry about the names so much not so important but really this is all about how we describe
再一次不要担心这些名字不是那么重要，但实际上这就是我们如何描述的
things that happened in the past.
过去发生的事情。
And we want to focus on that being in the moment or actually experiencing that time because usually
我们希望专注于当下或实际体验那一刻，因为通常
when we use this either.
当我们使用它时。
Another thing was happening at the same time two things at the same time.
另一件事同时发生了两件事。
Or one thing was happening and something stopped it.
或者一件事正在发生，而某事阻止了它。
That's how we usually use this.
这就是我们通常使用它的方式。
Something was happening and then another very important thing went and stopped that thing or interrupted
某事正在发生，然后另一件非常重要的事情发生并停止或打断了那件事
it and we say that thing that was happening as a way to say basically a little bit of context or a little
它和我们说正在发生的事情是一种基本上说一点上下文或一点点的方式
bit of background before we say this really important thing.
在我们说这个非常重要的事情之前，先了解一下背景。
All right.
好的。
So let's talk about the first one.
那么让我们谈谈第一个。
First the one where there are two things going on.
首先是发生两件事的那个。
We use often was was or were.
我们经常使用 was was 或 were。
And then when we use the verb we use i n g we use i n g after it.
然后当我们使用动词时，我们使用 i n g 我们在它之后使用 i n g。
So if you use was and were the verb after it will usually be i n g.
所以如果你使用 was 和 were 后面的动词通常是 i n g。
And two things are happening at the same time.
有两件事同时发生。
He was he was he was playing football and she was watching watching what were watching him play football
他是他是他在踢足球，她在看什么在看他踢足球
but he was playing football and she was watching if we use we then we would say we were right.
但他在踢足球，她在看，如果我们使用我们，那么我们会说我们是对的。
He was playing football and we were watching two things going on same time one action this person one
他在踢足球，我们在看两件事同时发生一个动作这个人一个
action she or one action we.
行动她或我们的一项行动。
OK that one's pretty simple.
好的，这很简单。
The other one actually is a little bit more common.
另一个实际上更常见一些。
So let me race this and then we'll look at the other one.
所以让我比赛这个，然后我们再看看另一个。
All right.
好的。
Now for this one we often use this one when we're telling stories because some important thing happened
现在我们在讲故事时经常使用这个，因为发生了一些重要的事情
in the story and we want to give a little bit of background information about the thing that was happening
在故事中，我们想提供一些关于正在发生的事情的背景信息
right before that important thing.
就在那重要的事情之前。
OK.
好的。
So we have an action.
所以我们有一个行动。
We have an action that's going on.
我们正在进行一项行动。
And then do the thing stops it.
然后做事情阻止它。
We often say but when is probably the most common.
我们经常说但何时可能是最常见的。
Sometimes we also use until and then when we say the second action that one should be just simple past.
有时，当我们说第二个动作应该只是过去时，我们也会使用 until 和 then 。
So was I and G were i n g and then h until.
I 和 G 也是如此，然后是 h，直到。
When and then simple past.
什么时候再简单过去。
Let me give you an example.
让我给你举个例子。
All right.
好的。
Example example I was I was eating I was eating lunch when Hey.
示例 我正在吃饭 我正在吃午饭 嘿。
When.
什么时候。
OK.
好的。
So eat was eating lunch when.
所以吃就是吃午饭的时候。
Now the important thing happens.
现在重要的事情发生了。
I got simple pass I got a phone call or a phone call and then we can say what the phone call was about.
我得到了简单的通行证，我接到一个电话或一个电话，然后我们可以说出电话的内容。
I got a phone call from my sister who told me that blah blah blah blah blah.
我接到姐姐打来的电话，她告诉我，胡说八道。
Something important happened something terrible happened Something great happened.
发生了重要的事，发生了可怕的事，发生了大事。
Whatever.
任何。
But we use this to give a little bit of background before the phone call.
但是我们在打电话之前用它来提供一些背景知识。
This is really really common.
这真的很常见。
So here's another one we were waiting for the call or the gift or the letter or whatever it doesn't
所以这是另一个我们在等待电话或礼物或信件或其他任何不
matter.
事情。
We were waiting for the call but it never came.
我们一直在等电话，但它从来没有来过。
We were waiting for the call were waiting but it never came came as the simple past tense.
我们正在等待电话正在等待，但它从未以简单的过去时态出现。
OK.
好的。
That was pretty simple as well.
那也很简单。
We want to focus on the fact that it didn't come OK.
我们想专注于它没有来的事实。
It never came.
它从来没有来过.
But we want to say we were waiting to give us a feeling that this is an important thing that this didn't
但我们想说，我们正在等待给我们一种感觉，这是一件重要的事情，而这并没有
happen.
发生。
This is really making me angry.
这真的让我很生气。
We waited 10 10 weeks for this letter to come and it never came right.
我们等了 10 到 10 周才收到这封信，但它从来没有来过。
So you can show your frustration by using this.
因此，您可以通过使用它来表达您的挫败感。
Were waiting was waiting OK.
正在等待等待确定。
She was speaking about her passion for accounting.
她谈到了她对会计的热情。
It's a little boring right until someone sets an M someone in the audience stood up and said Stop
有点无聊，直到有人设置一个M 观众中有人站起来说停止
ok.
好的。
So put quotes around this to me OK so said is the simple past.
所以给我加上引号好吧，这么说是简单的过去。
That's the thing that happened.
这就是发生的事情。
But if someone just stood up and said Stop there would be no context no situation.
但是，如果有人只是站起来说停止，就没有上下文没有情况。
If we say she spoke and someone stood up and said Stop that's not really what was happening before it
如果我们说她说话了，有人站起来说停止，那并不是之前发生的事情
doesn't give us a feeling of this action and then push something that completely stops it.
不会给我们这种动作的感觉，然后推动完全阻止它的东西。
So we need to use was speaking here she was speaking until someone in the audience stood up and said
所以我们需要用 was speak here she was speak 直到观众中有人站起来说
Stop Now that's kind of a weird example but hopefully it gives you an idea for why we would use was
Stop Now 这是一个奇怪的例子，但希望它能让你了解我们为什么要使用 is
or were plus I N G and then use the simple past.
或者分别加 I N G 然后用一般过去时。
And I want to make make sure I'm clear that I'm not trying to offend any accountants out there if you're
我想确保我很清楚，如果你是
an accountant.
一个会计师。
I admire you because I think accounting is a little boring.
我很佩服你，因为我觉得会计有点无聊。
And so if you're able to do something that's very hard I respect you.
因此，如果您能够做一些非常困难的事情，我尊重您。